Hello everyone, in this session, I will demo how to generate TK using GitHub Corvallis.
To use this feature, first, I need to have TWSFounder created for the item I need to generate TK.
In this session, I will go to Team Support. Here, I will have two options.
The first option is to create TWSFounder for an item.
And the second option is to create TWSFounder for a list of other items.
I will demo the first option first. I will choose One Item here.
Here, I will have three different types of information.
The first information is the TWSFounder.
The first information is the database part.
This is the folder part that contains the database that I have logged from the snapshot.
The second information is the workspace part.
I will create a blank folder.
And I will take this folder part to contain the outputs in the TUN running process.
The third information is the item name.
This is the name of the item that I need to create.
The TWSFounder.
After I have filled out these three things, I will click on Generate Environment.
After completing this step, TUN will show me an option to notify me.
At the same time, TUN Visual Studio Code will automatically open the TUN Studio Code.
This is the first step.
TuneVisualStudioCode will automatically open and save the space folder of the item you need to create.
Here I will have the source file.
I will also have two files.
The first is test.cpp and the second is test.h.
They are here.
Besides, I can use the OpenOutput function.
It will help me to open and save the space folder of the item I need to create.
For the second option, I will choose ListItem.
I also have three important information.
The first is database bars.
The second one is the first option.
And the third one is ListItemBars.
I will have an Excel file to store the information of the item name and item bars.
I also need to create a SpaceFolder.
Then I will take the bar of this file and store it in TuneVisualStudioCode.
I need to open it to the third room.
Then I will click on Generate Environment.
Hello everyone, welcome back to my channel, today I will share with you how to create a
free e-mail account, you can use the link in the description of this video,
you can use the link in the description of this video,
I choose Generate Test Case by A.I.Copilot
Here, I have two main sources of information
The first one is the item bar
I will go to the TestWorksBaseFounder of an item
called Generate Test Case
For example, this item
I will copy the bar of this file
After that, I will input the first source of information
And the next one is the data base bar
Just like the previous step
I will also input the data of the folder containing the data base
Here, then I will type autodefine object here
In the process of running
I can
follow the information directly
by clicking on the Show Execution Log here
There is a Terminal window that will appear
and will show the information
while I am running
The Terminal window will appear
For example, if you want to run the test
You can change the Terminal data
You can see the information here
I will then select the Terminal data
The Terminal data is displayed here
In this way, we can control the power
The cluster can be used for my test
The computer will be able to control the volume of the data
and the pressure and the voltage
It is possible to give a higher or lower value
by pressing the Error button
For simple data, the computer will not ever
press the Error button
Please subscribe to La La School channel to not miss the fascinating videos
Thanks for watching
Subscribe to La La School channel to not miss the fascinating videos
Please subscribe to La La School channel to not miss the fascinating videos
Thanks for watching
Subscribe to La La School channel to not miss the fascinating videos
Please subscribe to La La School channel to not miss the fascinating videos
At the end of Auto Default Check, we will go to the next step, which is Repair Get Suits.
In the pop-up information, we will see that there are 3 functions, Forward, Suits Function, and Update Lockdown.
We see that there are 3 functions listed here.
We will select one of the 3 functions that we want to generate test case.
In the next step, we will have 2 options.
The first option is to generate test case for the function we are selecting here.
And the second option is to generate test case for all functions in this item.
To make it easier for us to observe the running process,
while generating test case, we will open Visual Studio Code
And we just which test.
So we set the default setting as 250,
and by this setting, we will detect whether the scale of the возь Dun move like this
So we design and import this item, that will open called feeds of it got.
We will see the information in the Visual Studio Code.
We will go to Output and choose GitHub Copilot Chart here.
The button generation information will be shown in this terminal.
After we see the notification that the test generation is completed,
that is, the button generation is done.
Next, we will click on Terminal.
We will build this test.
Here we have 8 TKs and all 8 TKs are passed.
Next, we will see the code code.
How does it work?
Then we will proceed to build Canada for this test.
We will click on Build Canada here.
After building Canada is done,
we will see that in the folder,
in the folder of the item,
we will see that there is a Canada folder in the Output folder.
We will open Canada.
Click on Tools.
Then we will go to the C folder.
Choose TCC.
Go to Tools.
Go to Canada.
Then we will open this tool.
We will create a project in Canada.
C Project.
In Canada.
We have Welcome C.
For this project,
if we wanted to start the project in Canada,
we have always selected Canada.
Any more,
I will not click here.
conjunct...
Then select Canada.
C will assume Canada future.
and select the year that we wanted to create.
We also select Canada,
and select the year that we want to create.
Here we go.
Then select the year that we want to create.
management,
Under Canada.
We select Canada.
now đ:// Almost Canada,
where this is Canada.
I will click on this .cov file
Then I will open this file
Here I see that the first function
its light code lines are blue
This is equivalent to the fact that this light code has been covered
And these red lines are still not covered
Then I will demo my second option
is Generate TK Onshoot
Before clicking on this Generate button
I will delete the newly created TKs
In the first option
to avoid being duplicated for the next time
Then I will click on Generate TK Onshoot here
to create TKs for all functions in this item
And this time I will click on Generate TK Onshoot
To create the second TK
and click on the next TK
to add the code
Then I will have to assign these first 2 TKs
on each TK
All 4 TKs
The first TKs will be the TKs
That's all
Now we go to the next TK
and then we will create the second TK
Let me go to the next TK
The second TK will be a small wall
The first one is here
So I just need to delete it
Please subscribe to La La School channel to not miss the fascinating videos
Thanks for watching
After finished generating the key for 3 functions in this item, I will build the data
In this step, I can click on the button
to open the data
I can build the data from the Visual Studio Code
I go to Terminal, select Runtasks, and select the data
In the Terminal section, I can see the values and codecodes that I have created
I will go to Toolkartata
I will see which codecodes have been created
I will gradually drag the Kantata folder into the project
To this Kantata
To this Kantata folder
Click Esto
Here we can see that the codecodes of the three functions of this item are already created
And so the color of these changes into blue
Now we click on Kantata to select View
Then we need to backup our API
We can choose View, Reboot Viewer to view this report
We can view the test report here
And the coverage that we can see here
This is the end of my demo
Thank you for watching